<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Space Rocks</string>
    <string name="start_game">Play</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="donate">Web</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="volume">Volume</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="particledetail">Particle detail</string>
    <string name="uidetail">Interface detail</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="low">Low</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="sound">Sound</string>
    <string name="menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="game_over">Game Over</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="rocks">Rocks</string>
    <string name="pups">Power Ups</string>
    <string name="laser">Laser</string>
    <string name="sonic_blast">Sonic Blast</string>
    <string name="black_hole">Black Hole</string>
    <string name="health">Health</string>
    <string name="energy">Energy</string>
    <string name="topguns">Top Guns</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="topgun">Top Gun</string>
    <string name="newtopgun">Enter your initials for placement upon the list of Top Guns.</string>
    <string name="letterpicker">"ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ "</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="continuebutton">Continue</string>
    <string name="developedby">Developed By:</string>
    <string name="poweredby">Powered By:</string>
    <string name="frenchtranslation">French Translation:</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="artist">Artist</string>
    <string name="album">Album</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="tutorial0">Welcome to Space Rocks!\n\nIn Space Rocks you command a small space craft caught in the midst of dangerous space debris. When a piece of debris collides with your craft it causes damage, large debris causes more damange than small and faster moving debris causes more damage than slow. In the following lessons you will learn how to pilot your craft and destroy the debris which threatens your survival!\n\nClick next to begin.</string>
    <string name="tutorial1">This is your space craft, the SR-2. Armed with lasers and bombs it is a capable craft that probably won\'t last all that long.</string>
    <string name="tutorial2">Move your space craft by dragging the virtual thumb stick in the direction you wish your craft to move.</string>
    <string name="tutorial3">Lasers are your primary weapon. Toggle auto fire on and off by tapping the auto fire button.</string>
    <string name="tutorial4">When equipped with sonic bombs you can deploy one by tapping the drop bomb button. Sonic Bombs will destroy all debris in the immediate vicinity.</string>
    <string name="tutorial5">Your hit points are displayed by the meter on the right side of your heads up display. When this meter is empty the game is over.</string>
    <string name="tutorial6">Your weapon energy is displayed by the meter on the left side of your heads up display. This meter drains while you fire lasers. As your weapon energy decreases so too will your rate of fire.</string>
    <string name="tutorial7">In Space Rocks there are three different types of power ups you can collect to help you along the way.</string>
    <string name="tutorial8">The most common power up is the purple energy bolt. Use this power up to replenish your weapon energy.</string>
    <string name="tutorial9">Obviously the red heart power up will replenish your hit points.</string>
    <string name="tutorial10">The blue sonic bomb power up will add one sonic bomb to your arsenal. These can be fairly rare so be on the look out.</string>
    <string name="tutorial11">Power ups are stored in special types of space rocks. You will find energy and sonic bomb power ups by destroying rocks with yellow crystals and hit point power ups are contained within blue crystal rocks.</string>
    <string name="tutorial12">Beware, destroying yellow crystal rocks will occasionally result in a dangerous black hole! A black hole will attract space rocks and accelerate them to high speeds.</string>
    <string name="tutorial13">If you are nearby when a black hole dissipates it will release any power ups it has absorbed.</string>
    <string name="tutorial14">This concludes the Space Rocks tutorial.\n\nEnjoy&#x2026;</string>
    <string name="donateprompt">Selecting Continue will open the web browser on your device and direct it to my webpage.</string>
    <string name="preloadchars">ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz0123456789!@#$%^&amp;*()-_+=*/\\:;\"&lt;&gt;,.?{}[]|`~\'&#x2026;</string>
</resources>
